<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Blogs on End Bad Design</title>
    <link>http://endbaddesign.com/blog/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Blogs on End Bad Design</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 18 Jul 2017 23:29:27 -0500</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="http://endbaddesign.com/blog/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Church Websites Part 2</title>
      <link>http://endbaddesign.com/blog/church-websites-part-2/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 18 Jul 2017 23:29:27 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://endbaddesign.com/blog/church-websites-part-2/</guid>
      <description>This week will be a continuation of last weeks post on Church Websites. Last week focused on the function of your website, and what information is important for you to display. Now we can focus on making your website more aesthetically pleasing to the people viewing it.
 &amp;ldquo;We don&amp;rsquo;t have the budget for a professional designer, how can we have a better-looking site?&amp;rdquo;
 This is the question I get asked the most.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Church Websites</title>
      <link>http://endbaddesign.com/blog/church-websites/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 13 Jul 2017 23:30:57 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://endbaddesign.com/blog/church-websites/</guid>
      <description>Your Church Website Part 1 - Function This week I want to talk about church websites. More importantly, the function of a church website. Next week we will get deeper into the aesthetics of your website, but this week will be concentrated on ensuring you have a functional, easy to use website.
In our digital, fast-paced world today, it is so important for your church to not only have a website but to have a good website.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Tools I Use</title>
      <link>http://endbaddesign.com/blog/tools-i-use/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 03 Jul 2017 22:37:56 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://endbaddesign.com/blog/tools-i-use/</guid>
      <description>Tools I Use Every good craftsman needs a good set of tools to do his job properly. Over the years a veteran craftsman will accumulate a lot of tools in his toolbox.
Working in design is no different. Over the years I have tried countless apps, programs, extensions, and hardware. Some of them I still use today, while others have been replaced or are no longer needed.
For this week&amp;rsquo;s post, I am going to list all of the tools I am currently using along with a few that I have used in the past but may still be useful.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Connect Card</title>
      <link>http://endbaddesign.com/blog/the-connect-card/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 28 Jun 2017 12:02:16 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://endbaddesign.com/blog/the-connect-card/</guid>
      <description>The Connect Card Let&amp;rsquo;s talk about the connect card, info card, guest card, visitor information card, follow up card or whatever name you might use to get contact information from your guest.
Connect cards are something that you usually have designed, print a couple thousand of and then you never think about them again. You get used to seeing them, the staff gets used to them and sometimes your guest quit filling them out.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Tear Down the Wall (of text)</title>
      <link>http://endbaddesign.com/blog/tear-down-the-wall-of-text/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 Jun 2017 22:27:02 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://endbaddesign.com/blog/tear-down-the-wall-of-text/</guid>
      <description>Tear Down the Wall (of text) This weeks blog post will be tackling the issue that everyone has probably faced at one time or another. The issue of how much text should be on a worship slide, sermon graphic or even a postcard mailout.
It is normal to want to put as much information as possible into a design especially when it is something that will be used to advertise an event or special service.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>An Introduction</title>
      <link>http://endbaddesign.com/blog/an-introduction/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 17 Jun 2017 19:01:31 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://endbaddesign.com/blog/an-introduction/</guid>
      <description>Welcome to the End Bad Design blog My name is Anthony Roberts and I hope that anyone involved in creative ministries at their church can benefit from this blog.
Most of you probably attend a church like me and do not have a large budget for your printing, graphic design and other creative services. Maybe you are the entire creative department by yourself.
Regardless of your situation or department size, there are many things you can do to make your church design better.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>